<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>#TidyTuesday on Anecdotal Evidence</title>
    <link>/tags/#tidytuesday/</link>
    <description>Recent content in #TidyTuesday on Anecdotal Evidence</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018 Tim Steggall.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/#tidytuesday/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>#TidyTuesday 2019 Week 1: #Rstats Tweets</title>
      <link>/post/rstats-tweets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/rstats-tweets/</guid>
      <description>Happy New Year! This first TidyTuesday dataset of 2019 was a great way to get the year started. I’ve been working on a separate side project that will include analyzing social media trends, so I thought this would be a good opportunity to test out at least one rough idea I’ve been kicking around.
I wanted to plot the most popular topics (as measured by word/token frequency) chronologically, to see if any particular keywords were unique to certain timeframes, and/or their frequency of use stood out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#TidyTuesday Week 37: NYC Restaurant Inspections</title>
      <link>/post/tidytuesday-nycrestaurants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/tidytuesday-nycrestaurants/</guid>
      <description>Week 2! Again, I found the most difficult part of this process to be diving into a random set of data and trying to pull out something interesting. Toss me some baseball or political data, and I have an idea of the questions I want to ask, but data on NYC restaurant inspections is a little trickier.
In the NYC Restaurant Inspections data each row is a unique inspection/violation - so one restaurant may have multiple records from the same date, but with different violations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#TidyTuesday Week 36: Medium Blog Posts</title>
      <link>/post/tidy-tuesday-medium/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/tidy-tuesday-medium/</guid>
      <description>So my first attempt at a #TidyTuesday - it’s not quite as easy as DRob makes it look! The data on Medium blog posts was interesting and in good shape, but for my first #TidyTuesday post I had a bit of a brain cramp generating ideas. I’ve been listening to a podcast lately that talks about the importance of a consistent posting schedule for bloggers, so I tried to dig into the relationship between an author’s posting schedule and the number of claps they receive.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>